So I hear all the ruckus right now. And that's exactly what it is. It is ruckus. And I think
people are not seeing the bigger play here. And that's what most concerns me. The bigger play
here is to disenfranchise the American people. They're doing it in the exact same way that they
did the Palestinian people. And I don't think people see that. And so they're having all of
these conversations that are not actually addressing the root. So we can sit here and
go on and on and on about Democrats and Republicans, but we are failing to see the actual shared
context. And it's been the shared context for a very long time. It's just that most of us didn't
really know about it because we weren't in the mix. And I'm sure I look like an outlier.
I'm sure I look like an outlier in saying this because it's a lot easier for folks to talk about
the things that are right here on the surface, which is Democrats versus Republicans. And that's
not what this is about. That's not what this is about by any means. There's a bigger play happening
here. There's a higher hand at work. And there's very much so not any addressing the realities of
that. The fact that you cannot talk about Israel should let you know that that is who is running
the show, period. That is who's running the show. Zionism is running the show. That's who's running
the show. So the fact that we have elected officials that are not addressing Zionism lets you know that
that is who is running the show. They are paid by who's running the show. So all of this talk about,
oh, the Republicans aren't doing this and the Democrats aren't doing this. That's not what it's
about. And anyone who is failing to acknowledge the actual presence of Zionism in this conversation
is someone you shouldn't be listening to. And I really want to really bring that to your attention
because the effort that is being put forth right now is an effort to literally create a populace that
is unable to fight for themselves and unwilling to. And many people think that that's been happening
solely at the behest of an American. And that's been happening solely at the behest of like keeping
America on top. Zionism is a political ideology that centers, that uses Judaism to center white Jewish
supremacy and colonialism. It is an expansion of the colonial project that is grounded in supremacy,
white supremacy. And it is very much aligned with capitalism. Not very much. It is grounded in
capitalism and the expansion of imperialism. And again, it is, it uses Judaism as a cover for white
supremacy and colonialist expansion. And so as we find a world that is continuing to wake up to the power of
indigenous people, the necessity for land back, the necessity for socialism, we see that there is a more
potent political ideology that is coming into play that is decisively against all of those things. And you know that
it is decisively against all of those things because you have been able to see how it addresses all of those
things in Palestine. You've been able to see that it has an apartheid government in Israel. You've been able to
see that it is deeply committed to torture and to imprisonment of anyone who does not adhere to their
ideologies. It is a fascist movement. So that is what we are up against. And it meshes perfectly with MAGA
who are all about racism, who are all about capitalism, which at the end of the day is about a usurping of
resources. So that's why you have a distinct separation within the MAGA world because you have MAGA folks that are
like, okay, we're actually not about like, you have MAGA folks whose racism is actually grounded in
white American supremacy. That's a very specific thing. It's white American supremacy. And they are
like, well, if we are supposed to be about us, why do we keep putting all this energy and all this money
over there? And that lets you know, it's not about us. They just use them. This is really about something
much deeper and much bigger. And I've been finding myself a bit disoriented in the past few days, like
just starting to feel like I'm kind of not, oh, now Instagram is messing with the comments. So I can't
see any of your comments at present. Um, I've been really like frustrated because I'm like, I feel
like I'm, I can tell when my analysis has like plateaued. I can tell when my analysis has plateaued
because I start to feel like disoriented. I start to feel like I'm not like I'm missing things. Right.
And I realized like, oh, your analysis has plateaued because you're starting to feel disoriented and like
you're missing things. And that means that you then have to dig deeper. And so when this government
shutdown moved on, and now you're seeing that the individuals who have chosen to vote, uh, to support
the shutdown opening, even though they didn't get anything in return for it, um, have, you know,
all of them aren't, none of them are up for reelection. So none of them have to do the whole,
like, I'm not taking money from APAC dance. When you see that Chuck Schumer, um, for the record,
you see people saying like, it's over for Chuck Schumer. The thing that fascinates me about all of
this is that people be acting like they're doing all this analysis. And at the end of the day, like
these conversations are being had far beyond anybody here and the knowledge of anybody here.
So like when I'm seeing folks on the news, have these conversations, again, you're having the
conversation you're allowed to have, which means you're not having the real conversation. And that's
the end of it. Journalism used to be having the conversations that the powers that be were not
having. It used to be investigative by a craft. Like the craft of journalism was investigative.
It wasn't an actual corner of journalism. It was the actual craft. Journalism as an actual
skillset was about finding out the truth. And then we had these factions of journalism turn up.
You know, the fact that people will call themselves a journalist because they're a gossip colonist.
Like that's not finding the truth. That's you being nosy and actually disregarding people's privacy.
That's what that is. But the reality of journalism should be being nosy and disregarding the secrecy
around the actual spaces that are exploiting the people. That's what it's supposed to do.
Okay. And whenever it does that effectively, it gets shut down because those spaces are actually
very, very effectively not wanting the people to move. They don't want the people to rise.
They don't want the people to know the truth because if you know the truth, then you will
actually possibly do something about it. But if you watch even just movies about journalists,
you're like, oh, wait a minute. These folks was actually about something.
Like it wasn't just like, oh, we, we do the news. No, it was, we find the truth.
It was, we find the truth. So when you watch movies like all the president's men and the, the paper
and the post and, um, there was another one about the Iraq war. Um, you know, all of these movies,
all these films bring it back to you that what we are in is not a space of truth.
So I know that you're seeing a lot of folks that are talking on mainstream media and they're all
talking nonsense. So just let me say that they're all talking nonsense. None of them are doing any
deep, really any, any real analysis. They are literally just reading headlines and then
regurgitating it to you. They're not considering anything beyond what's in front of them. They are
not intellectual. They are literally just like, okay, I'm going to bring people on here. And nine times
out of 10, even when they have the best of intentions, they bring people on there and they
just kind of talk about it on a surface level. And then they move on because there isn't even enough
time. There isn't even enough time, but they really like being on TV. So they stay on TV, right?
They like that check. They like the, the, the experience of it. So they stay there. Um, fast forward,
you have folks like on this internet and there's so much really important acknowledgement that's
happening, right? You have people that are pointing out like, Hey, the Democrats never actually
wanted to do anything for you, which is obvious. You have people pointing out like, Hey, these are
the Democrats that actually went along with the shutdown being lifted and not getting anything
to protect Medicare, Medicaid, ACA. Hey, all of that is necessary. The next step in that alignment is
why? And it's not simply just to make people rich. And I need folks to really understand that
because I think that is the limitation of an arm of our analysis. And so we have a lot
of like eat the rich and you know, we have a lot of like, Oh, like we need to bring down
the billionaires and that as important and necessary as it is, is actually not the full
depth of what has to happen. The billionaires are actually serving a greater issue. They're
serving a greater issue of colonialism, a greater issue of exploitation of the earth and of its
peoples. And that issue is not simply just because of money. That issue is bolstered by a political
ideology beyond simply just, I want money. And so if you're not addressing the political ideology
that bolsters that, then you're not really addressing that. You're talking about it because
it's necessary to acknowledge that these billionaires are the problem, but we're not addressing what is
the problem of the billionaires. What is allowing them to continue? And it's an ideology and it's
Zionism and it is pervasive and it is global. And there are parties that may not be Zionist,
but understand how they can use it to their advantage, right? Parties like, you know, folks
like Modi in, in, in Italy. I mean, sorry, in India, you know, the chick in Italy.
Um, uh, your man's in, in, uh, is it Turkey or Hungary? I think it's in Turkey. Like all of these
dictators, they understand that Zionism allows them to continue to be dictators because it is
fascist by nature. So they're like, Oh, if I serve it, then I'm good. So, um, you know, that's where we're
at. So in my opinion, all of this at its root is at the behest of Zionists who want to usurp the United
States and the globe. And, uh, they've been practicing in Palestine by getting their, their,
getting their gear together, getting their, their surveillance together, getting all the weapons
together. They've been practicing the best ways to brainwash a people to support that movement.
They've been practicing the best ways to diminish a people who would fight that movement. And we are
watching in real time, those things be supplanted right here in the United States. So I don't have
much to say about Democrats and Republicans. They are all a part of the brainwash people who have been
co-opted to carry forth this movement. And this movement is one that is happening at this apex at a
real time, which is also why this is a spiritual war, because if you're using spirituality as the, as, as if
you're weaponizing spirituality, it becomes a spiritual war and they are weaponizing Judaism. Thank you for
coming to my Ted talk. Oh.
Oh.